Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Ed George papers, 1938-2013 and undated RL.00703
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
J. Walter Thompson Company. Ed George papers
1938-2013 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
J. Walter Thompson Company
RL.00703
14.2 Linear Feet
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
However, original audiovisual materials are closed until use copies can be produced.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. There may be a 48-hour delay in obtaining these materials.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The J. Walter Thompson Company. Ed George papers were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a transfer in 2001, with a subsequent gift in 2009 and 2015.
Biographical Note
The J. Walter Thompson Company (JWT) was founded in New York, N.Y., in 1864, and is one of the world's largest advertising agencies. Edward Acheson George was an Creative Director and executive at several JWT offices.
Ed George was born 1935. Education: Tulane University. JWT Chicago: Vice President, Associate Creative Director 1956-1973; Foote Cone & Belding/Los Angeles: Associate Creative Director 1973-1975; JWT Detroit: Senior Vice President, Co-Creative Director 1975-1980; Playboy: Vice President and Creative Director 1980; JWT Los Angeles: Vice President, Creative Director 1981-approximately 1986.
Collection Overview
Collection includes correspondence, reports, scripts, tear sheets and other printed materials; drawings, sketches, cartoons, paintings, storyboards and packaging designs; and audiovisual materials (phonograph records, videocassettes, audio tapes). Companies represented include Burger King, Champion, Eaton, Faygo, Foote Cone & Belding, Ford, Hawaii Express, Kawasaki, Liggett & Myers, Mazda, Monroe, Oscar Mayer, Parker Pen, Playboy, and Seven-Up. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
Advertising agencies; Advertising -- History; Advertising agencies -- Employees; Advertising agencies -- Executives; Advertising agencies -- United States -- History; Advertising agencies -- United States; Commercial art; Advertising, Outdoor -- Posters; Billboards -- Design and construction; Billboards; Memorabilia; Packaging; Audiotapes; Billboards -- United States; Filmstrips; Phonograph records; Videocassettes; George, Ed; John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History; Burger King Corporation; Champion Spark Plug (Company); Eaton Corporation; Foote, Cone & Belding; Ford Motor Company; Liggett & Myers Tobacco Company; Oscar Mayer & Co; Seven-Up Company
- Personal and Professional Files, 1950-2013 and undated; 1
  - General Files, 1950-2013 and undated; 1
    - Awards, 1987-1998 (Box 1)
    - Bell System, undated (Box 1)
    - Biographical, undated (Box 1)
    - Boats (brochures, blueprints, etc.), 1968-1973 (Box 1)
    - Ed George Communications, 2013 (Box 1)
    - Edward C. George--Scrapbook on election to Board of Harriman Ripley, 1950 (Box 1)
    - Farewell poster--"This Is the Army, Mr. George!", undated (Box 18)
    - Ford, 1984-1987 (Box 1)
    - Ford--Product planners speech, 1997 (Box 1)
    - Kawasaki, 1982-1983 (Box 1)
    - Miscellaneous, 1966-1995 (Box 1)
    - Miscellaneous cartoons, undated (Box 1)
    - Mr. Giggles, 1969 (Box 1)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 1)
    - Photographs--Airplane production stills, 1980 (Box 1)
    - Photographs--Eaton Truck Components, undated (Box 1)
    - Photographs--Ford outdoor (parts, service, used cars), 1970s (Box 1)
    - Photographs--Oscar Mayer (Ed George at work), undated (Box 1)
    - Playboy--Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1979-1980 (Box 1)
    - Playboy--Print advertisement, undated (Box 1)
    - Travel journal "This Is the Best Yet", 1958 (Box 1)
  - J. Walter Thompson Company, 1962-1994 and undated; 2
    - Commodore's Cup Regatta, 1987 (Box 1)
    - Correspondence and general, 1968-1991 (Box 1a)
    - Don Johnston, 1986-1987 (Box 1a)
    - Ed George resignation, 1994 (Box 1a)
    - Exploding Some Myths about Account Men (Granger Tripp), 1968 (Box 1a)
    - Indian File (Hindustan Thompson newsletter), 1971 (Box 1a)
    - James Webb Young saying (framed item), undated (Box 1a)
      Scope and Contents
      "For it is with the advertising man as with the cow: no browsing, no milk."
    - Los Angeles. And the Small Office Puzzle, 1984 (Box 1a)
    - Los Angeles Creative Philosophy, undated (Box 1a)
    - Los Angeles Office credentials, undated (Box 1a)
    - Marketing: The Key to the 90's, 1983 (Box 1a)
    - Memo writing guidelines, 1962 (Box 1a)
    - Personal portfolio, 1977 (Box 1a)
    - Team Kawasaki speech, 1982 (Box 1a)
  - Printed Material, 1962-1995 and undated; 3
    - Air & Space/Smithsonian--The Pursuit of Speed: The Airplane First to Fastest, 1992 (Box 17)
    - Cycle Magazine calendar pages, images of vintage motorcycles, 1988 (Box 7)
    - Daimler Benz 100th anniversary booklet, 1986 (Box 7)
    - Ferrari--Bruce Miller posters, undated (Box 23)
    - Ford collateral literature (Mustang, Windstar catalogs), 1994-1995 (Box 2)
    - Ford Motorsports RS200 catalog (Canada), 1987 (Box 7)
    - Ford Truck 75th anniversary, 1992 (Box 7)
    - Harley Davidson catalog, 1989 (Box 7)
    - J. Walter Thompson Los Angeles Office Creative Philosophy, 1982 (Box 10)
    - Lighthouses of Michigan calendar, 1989 (Box 7)
    - Link Freeman Advertising brochure, undated (Box 2)
    - Memoirs of Biff Gumsley, undated (Box 2)
      (David Field/West End Studios publication)
    - Nissan Z catalog, 1991 (Box 7)
    - Owens Illinois beer bottle poster, undated (Box 23)
    - Playboy Jazz Festival guide, 1980 (Box 2)
    - Popular Mechanics--The Hand Plane insert, 1990 (Box 16)
    - Printing Salesman's Herald (Champion Papers), 1969 (Box 2)
    - Sports Car Coloring Book (Ron Nelson, John Ferree), 1962 (Box 2)
  - Promotional Items, Memorabilia, 1989 and undated; 4
    - Cigarette packaging models, undated (Box 3)
      Includes: Chesterfield 17, Chesterfield Carolinas, Dorado Slims
    - Faygo Cola button, undated (Box 3)
    - Ford alarm clock, undated (Box 3)
    - Ford truck mug, undated (Box 3)
    - Hamm's beer cans, undated (Box 3)
    - J. Walter Thompson 125th anniversary license plate, 1989 (Box 3)
    - J. Walter Thompson 125th anniversary medal in box, 1989 (Box 3)
    - J. Walter Thompson Los Angeles ashtray, undated (Box 3)
    - J. Walter Thompson Summer Picnic Frisbee, undated (Box 3)
    - Ken-L Ration "My Dog" record jacket, undated (Box 3)
    - Name plates, undated (Box 3)
    - Oscar Mayer Weinermobile toy, undated (Box 3)
    - Schlitz tap handle, undated (Box 3)
- Artwork, Cartoons, Designs, Illustrations, 1970-1995 and undated; 2
  - Advertising agency satires, undated (Box 2)
  - Advertising agency satires, undated (Box 7)
  - All Sports Magazine, undated (Box 8)
  - All Sports News, undated (Box 11)
  - Automotive designs, undated (Box 7)
  - Birthday and Valentine's cards, undated (Box 7)
  - Birthday cartoons, undated (Box 18)
  - Bluenote GPC logo, undated (Box 17)
  - Booth Newspapers, undated (Box 8)
  - Burger King, undated (Box 2)
  - "Bula" Dogs (Oscar Mayer?), undated (Box 2)
  - "Bula" Dogs (Oscar Mayer?), 1990 (Box 7)
  - Car and Driver Magazine, 1988-1990 (Box 4)
  - Champion, undated (Box 2)
  - Champion, undated; 2 folders (Box 8)
  - Chicago Tribune outdoor, undated; 4 folders (Box 20)
  - Claussen outdoor, undated (Box 20)
  - Comics and sketches, undated; 5 folders (Box 4)
  - Cycle World, undated (Box 2)
  - Detroit Grand Prix, 1984; 5 folders (Box 11)
  - Eaton Truck Components, undated; 5 folders (Box 8)
  - Foote Cone & Belding/LA--Mazda, 1970s and undated (Box 23)
  - Foote Cone & Belding/LA--Smokey the Bear, Taco Bell outdoor, United California Bank, 1970s and undated (Box 19)
  - Ford, undated; 3 folders (Box 2)
  - Ford, undated; 5 folders (Box 9)
  - Ford (dealer advertisements, outdoor), undated (Box 11)
  - Ford (Festiva), 1988; 12 folders (Box 12)
  - Ford (miscellaneous including Taurus, Probe, F Series, Christmas), 1989 and undated; 10 folders (Box 13)
  - Ford (miscellanous posters, outdoor), undated; 10 folders (Box 14)
  - Ford (Taurus print), approximately 1986; 4 folders (Box 15)
  - Ford (print), undated; 5 folders (Box 20)
  - Ford (outdoor), undated; 7 folders (Box 21)
  - Ford (used cars, parts, dealer outdoor), undated; 10 folders (Box 22)
  - Ford collateral literature mockups and designs, 1980s-1995; 5 folders (Box 4)
  - Ford collateral literature mockups and designs, 1980s-1995 (Box 5)
  - General Electric logo, undated (Box 7)
  - Hamm's beer, undated; 12 folders (Box 9)
  - Hammond Organ print, undated (Box 15)
  - Harley Davidson, undated (Box 10)
  - Hawaii Express Airlines, undated (Box 2)
  - Hawaii Express Airlines storyboards, undated; 3 folders (Box 15)
  - J. Walter Thompson logos, undated (Box 2)
  - J. Walter Thompson poster--JWT Advertising & Nifty Slogan Company, undated (Box 15)
  - JWT Chicago--Businessmen cartoons, Seven-Up, undated (Box 19)
  - JWT Detroit--Chatham Supermarkets, Ford, Jaguar, State of Michigan, WXYZ-TV, 1970s and undated (Box 19)
  - JWT/LA--Kawasaki, 1982 (Box 19)
  - JWT/NY--Burger King, Kodak, 1970s and undated (Box 19)
  - Johnson (?) outboard motor, undated (Box 10)
  - Kawasaki, 1982 and undated; 11 folders (Box 2)
  - Kawasaki, undated (Box 10)
  - Kawasaki, undated; 5 folders (Box 16)
  - Kawasaki, 1983 and undated (Box 17)
    Includes: Bob Steven photograph; San Jose Mile poster
  - Kawasaki brochure, 1982 (Box 4)
  - Kawasaki San Jose Mile transparency, 1983 (Box 7)
  - Ken-L Ration, undated (Box 16)
  - Ken-L Ration, undated (Box 17)
  - Kodak, undated (Box 10)
  - Liggett & Myers--Aspen Menthol, Richmond Straight Cut, Virginia Brights designs, undated; 26 folders (Box 6)
  - Logo designs, undated (Box 2)
  - Marine Corps, 1976 (Box 16)
  - Mazda, undated; 3 folders (Box 17)
  - Mazda, undated; 2 folders (Box 23)
  - Mazda storyboards, 1974 (Oversize-folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous illustrations, undated; 2 folders (Box 7)
  - Miscellaneous illustrations, undated; 2 folders (Box 16)
  - Miscellaneous illustrations, undated; 4 folders (Box 18)
    Includes: Ford, Hawaii Express, Kawasaki, Valentine's Day
  - Miscellaneous illustrations, undated (Box 19)
  - Miscellaneous illustrations, undated (Box 23)
  - Miscellaneous illustrations, undated (Oversize-folder 1)
  - Musicians, undated (Box 7)
  - Musicians, undated (Box 18)
  - Olivetti print, undated (Box 17)
  - Oscar Mayer, undated; 6 folders (Box 10)
  - Panoz Motorsports, undated (Box 19)
  - Parker Pen "Arrow" illustrations, undated (Box 2)
  - Parker Pen "Arrow" illustrations, undated (Box 17)
  - Payless Drug Stores, undated (Box 2)
  - Playboy (including Jazz Festival poster), 1980 and undated (Box 17)
  - Playboy (including Jazz Festival poster), 1980 and undated (Box 19)
  - RAT Brothers, undated (Box 17)
  - Seven-Up, undated (Box 10)
  - Seven-Up, undated (Box 17)
  - Seven-Up, 1970 (Box 23)
  - Seven-Up outdoor, undated; 5 folders (Box 22)
  - Seven-Up outdoor and storyboards, undated; 5 folders (Box 16)
  - Seven-Up outdoor poster sheets, undated (Box 24)
    Rolled items in tubes
  - Seven-Up outdoor poster sheets, undated (Box 25)
  - SOS Sports, undated (Box 17)
  - Sterling Beer, undated; 7 folders (Box 10)
  - Storyboards, undated (Box 23)
  - Sunkist, undated (Box 23)
  - Transparencies, undated (Box 10)
- Audiovisual Materials, 1938-1986 and undated; 3
  - D'Arcy--Bank Americard Chorus :30, undated (Box AV1, Film-reel RL00703-F16-001)
  - D'Arcy--Bank Americard Tuba Player :30, undated (Box AV1, Film-reel RL00703-F16-002)
  - Ed George reel, undated (Box AV2, Film-reel RL00703-F16-003)
  - Film Fair combination reel, undated (Box AV3, Film-reel RL00703-F16-004)
  - Food Play 2066B, undated (Box AV3, Film-reel RL00703-F16-005)
  - Hamm's--Bear Fisherman, undated (Box AV1, Film-reel RL00703-F16-006)
  - Hamm's--Bird :30, undated (Box AV1, Film-reel RL00703-F16-007)
  - Kawasaki compilation, undated (Box AV2, Film-reel RL00703-F16-008)
    Includes: 1980 Invader; Truck; Snowdrift; Parachute
  - Kawasaki--Truck :30, undated (Box AV1, Film-reel RL00703-F16-009)
  - Kawasaki--Truck :30, undated (Box AV1, Film-reel RL00703-F16-010)
  - Kawasaki--Truck :30, undated (Box AV1, Film-reel RL00703-F16-011)
  - Ken-L Ration Burger--Baa :30, undated (Box AV1, Film-reel RL00703-F16-012)
  - Ken-L Ration--Bashue :60, undated (Box AV1, Film-reel RL00703-F16-013)
  - Ken-L Ration Burger--Hotel :60, undated (Box AV1, Film-reel RL00703-F16-014)
  - Ken-L Ration Burger--Mother George :60, undated (Box AV1, Film-reel RL00703-F16-015)
  - Mazda--Cat and Mouse :30, undated (Box AV1, Film-reel RL00703-F16-016)
  - Monroe--Bandit :30, undated (Box AV1, Film-reel RL00703-F16-017)
  - Monroe--Bandit :30, undated (Box AV1, Film-reel RL00703-F16-018)
  - Monroe--Bandit :30, undated (Box AV1, Film-reel RL00703-F16-019)
  - Monroe--Bandit :30, undated (Box AV1, Film-reel RL00703-F16-020)
  - Monroe--Bandit :30, undated (Box AV1, Film-reel RL00703-F16-021)
  - Monroe--Shocktails :30, undated (Box AV1, Film-reel RL00703-F16-022)
  - Monroe--Shocktails 15/15 sec., undated (Box AV1, Film-reel RL00703-F16-023)
  - Murine--Black on White :30, undated (Box AV1, Film-reel RL00703-F16-024)
  - Murine--Cigar Chimneys :30, undated (Box AV1, Film-reel RL00703-F16-025)
  - Murine--Cloud Fist :30, undated (Box AV1, Film-reel RL00703-F16-026)
  - Murine--Eye Living :60, undated (Box AV1, Film-reel RL00703-F16-027)
  - Murine--Eye Living :60, undated (Box AV1, Film-reel RL00703-F16-028)
  - Oscar Mayer, undated (Box AV2, Film-reel RL00703-F16-029)
  - Oscar Mayer--Food Play Nutrition :60, undated (Box AV1, Film-reel RL00703-F16-030)
  - Oscar Mayer--Heavenly, undated (Box AV1, Film-reel RL00703-F16-031)
  - Oscar Mayer--Heavenly, undated (Box AV1, Film-reel RL00703-F16-032)
  - Oscar Mayer--Son of Hot Dog Stand :60, undated (Box AV1, Film-reel RL00703-F16-033)
  - Schlitz--Fisherman :10, undated (Box AV1, Film-reel RL00703-F16-034)
  - Schlitz--Hunter :10, undated (Box AV1, Film-reel RL00703-F16-035)
  - Schlitz--Soft Shoe :10, undated (Box AV1, Film-reel RL00703-F16-036)
  - Seven-Up--Big Can :10, undated (Box AV1, Film-reel RL00703-F16-037)
  - Seven-Up--Ed George compilation, undated (Box AV2, Film-reel RL00703-F16-038)
    Includes: Win Your Un Thing; Snake; Intermission; Missionaries; Food; Frog; Couple. Notes with reel)
  - Seven-Up--Missionaries, undated (Box AV1, Film-reel RL00703-F16-039)
  - Seven-Up--RTV-US, undated (Box AV3, Film-reel RL00703-F16-040)
  - Seven-Up--Reel--Couple 30 and 20 sec., undated (Box AV3, Film-reel RL00703-F16-041)
  - Seven-Up--Thank You America :60 and :30, undated (Box AV3, Film-reel RL00703-F16-042)
  - Seven-Up--Thank You America :30, undated (Box AV1, Film-reel RL00703-F16-043)
  - Seven-Up--Thank You America :30 live action, undated (Box AV1, Film-reel RL00703-F16-044)
  - Seven-Up--The Couple :30 reduction, undated (Box AV1, Film-reel RL00703-F16-045)
  - Seven-Up--Win Your Un Thing sweepstakes :60 and :30, undated (Box AV1, Film-reel RL00703-F16-046)
  - Seven-Up--Win Your Un Thing :60 and :30, undated (Box AV1, Film-reel RL00703-F16-047)
  - Simoniz Master Wax--Submarine :60, undated (Box AV1, Film-reel RL00703-F16-048)
  - Sterling Beer--Artwork :60, undated (Box AV1, Film-reel RL00703-F16-049)
  - Sterling Graphics--4 prints, original with eagle, undated (Box AV1, Film-reel RL00703-F16-050)
  - Theodore Hamm--Fisherman :60, undated (Box AV1, Film-reel RL00703-F16-051)
  - Untitled 5874, undated (Box AV3, Film-reel RL00703-F16-052)
  - Volvo--Car-Dog :60, undated (Box AV1, Film-reel RL00703-F16-053)
  - Seven-Up--Win Your Un Thing :60 and :30, 1969 (Box AV2, Film-reel RL00703-F35-001)
  - Seven-Up--Win Your Un Thing :60 and :30, 1969 (Box AV2, Film-reel RL00703-F35-002)
  - Bacharach, undated (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL00703-RR-001)
  - Bank Americard music, undated (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL00703-RR-002)
    Includes: Tuba, Chorus :30
  - Barney Kessel, undated (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL00703-RR-003)
  - Burger King--Alligator, undated (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL00703-RR-004)
  - Burger King--Compilation, 1976 (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL00703-RR-005)
    Includes: Show Us Your Smile :60 and :30; Kids/Show Us Your Smile :30
  - Burger King--Smile compilation, undated (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL00703-RR-006)
    Includes: All Burger King Smile; 2nd cut, ABC Saturday morning kids' show; Bugsy Moran
  - Burger King--Smile, undated (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL00703-RR-007)
  - Ed George at Boulevard jam session, undated (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL00703-RR-008)
  - Ed George at Boulevard session with Bob Ragland, undated (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL00703-RR-009)
  - Faygo Soft Drinks--Compilation, 1978 (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL00703-RR-010)
    Includes: Nobody Can Never Ever Outgrow Faygo; The Bigger the Thirst; The Best Things in Life; Faygo Cola Nuts
  - Faygo Soft Drinks--Compilation, undated (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL00703-RR-011)
  - Faygo Soft Drinks--Demo Cola Nuts (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL00703-RR-012)
  - Faygo Soft Drinks--TV songs, undated (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL00703-RR-013)
    Includes: Bouncing Boat; Rainbow Dance; Jump Rope/Diet
  - Goodbye, Nick--Demos, undated (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL00703-RR-014)
  - Goodbye, Nick--Compilation, undated (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL00703-RR-015)
    Includes: Good Bye Letter; Skin Diver; Foreign Legion; Peaceful Singer; Yong Yong Yong; Prize Fighter; Movie Star; Knife Thrower
  - Hammond Aquarius, undated (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL00703-RR-016)
  - J. Walter Thompson--Compilation, undated (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL00703-RR-017)
    Includes: Frito; Sunoco; Western
  - Joe Sicurella & Associates--Writer's Reel #1, undated (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL00703-RR-018)
    Includes work from Joe Raposo, Steve Benderoth, Michael Loving, Lynn Ahrens, Jon Silberman, Ginny Redington
  - Kawasaki--Dub of 3 radio beds, 1978 (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL00703-RR-019)
    Includes: Guys; Duet; Country
  - Kawasaki--Snowmobile TV track, undated (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL00703-RR-020)
    Includes: Parachute :30; Snowdrift :30
  - Kawasaki--TV music, "Saturday Night" :30, 1981 (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL00703-RR-021)
  - Kelso Herston Enterprises--Compilation, undated (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL00703-RR-022)
    Includes: Adorn; Burger King; Busch beer; Campbell's; Champion; Daisy Razor; Earthborn Shampoo; Firestone; Ford; GMC Trucks; Hamm's beer; Hormel; Huffy; Kawasaki; Levi; Monroe; Noxzema; Oscar Mayer; Pan Am; Pontiac; R.C. Cola; S&H Green Stamps; Sealy Mattress; Sears; Seven-Up; Tame; Uncle Ben; Water Pik; Wrigley's
  - Mazda--Boing Boing radio music only, undated (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL00703-RR-023)
  - Mazda--Scratch track "Cat and Mouse", 1974 (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL00703-RR-024)
  - Moby Dick, undated (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL00703-RR-025)
  - Music of Richard Egizi (extracted from scores), undated (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL00703-RR-026)
    Includes: Rock; Lush; Baroque; "Movin"; Here's That Rainy Day; Romantic; Hard to Describe
  - Norman Freehling testimonial dinner; Ed George master of ceremonies, 1963 (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL00703-RR-027)
  - Old Time Radio Themes, undated (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL00703-RR-028)
    Themes Like Old Times: 180 of the most famous oeiginal radio themes, volumes 1 and 2
  - Oscar Mayer, Sr., undated (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL00703-RR-029)
  - Oscar Mayer--Marching Club :60 and :20, undated (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL00703-RR-030)
  - Oscar Mayer--Music compilation, undated (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL00703-RR-031)
    Includes: Symphony; 6 ft. Fridge; Hero; Country Window; Tijuana instrumental; Bossa Nova; Hot Dog Stand; Ham; Doll House; Lost Dog; Slow Start; Spanish instrumental
  - Pepsi--International, The Whole World Over, 1983 (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL00703-RR-032)
  - Shield Productions--Intermission :30 and :20, undated (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL00703-RR-033)
  - Soundshop--Prime Cuts compilation, undated (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL00703-RR-034)
    Includes: Yamaha guitars; Fact Cigarettes; Silver Dollar City; Carson-Pirie-Scott; Country Hearth Bread; Baldwin Fun Machine; Dodge Dealers; Sunday's Chicken; Harley-Davidson; TV-12 Richmond; TV-6 Milwaukee; Child Life shoes; Billy Beer; Dales Shopping Center; McCarty State Pride chicken; Riceland Rice
  - Soundshop--Son of Scrabook, undated (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL00703-RR-035)
  - Sterling tape, undated (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL00703-RR-036)
  - Thumb piano--Jim Walsh :60, undated (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL00703-RR-037)
  - Wallace Fulton's Dinner, undated (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL00703-RR-038)
  - War of the Worlds (Orson Welles, Mercury Theater, 1938 (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL00703-RR-039)
  - Blue Cross :30, undated (Box AV4, Video-cassette RL00703-Umatic-001)
  - Ford--Electric Reindeer :30, 1985 (Box AV4, Video-cassette RL00703-Umatic-002)
  - Form and Function--With music fade 2:45, 1986 (Box AV4, Video-cassette RL00703-Umatic-003)
  - Form and Function 2, undated (Box AV4, Video-cassette RL00703-Umatic-004)
  - Hawaii Express--"Air to Air Footage" 20:00, 1983 (Box AV4, Video-cassette RL00703-Umatic-005)
  - Hawaii Express--Party :30, undated (Box AV4, Video-cassette RL00703-Umatic-006)
  - J. Walter Thompson--Detroit compilation, undated (Box AV4, Video-cassette RL00703-Umatic-007)
    Includes: Anco "Piano Movers"; Monroe "Stagecoach," "Filter Plus," "Bandit," "Sheriff"
  - J. Walter Thompson--Detroit K2, undated (Box AV4, Video-cassette RL00703-Umatic-008)
  - J. Walter Thompson--Detroit K part 1, undated (Box AV4, Video-cassette RL00703-Umatic-009)
  - Kawasaki--Compilation, 1982 (Box AV4, Video-cassette RL00703-Umatic-010)
    Includes: Stoplight; Road Race King; Stoplight 25/05
  - Kawasaki--Jetski :30, 1981 (Box AV4, Video-cassette RL00703-Umatic-011)
  - Kawasaki--Ponca City sales film, 1981 (Box AV4, Video-cassette RL00703-Umatic-012)
  - Kawasaki--Rocky :35, 1982 (Box AV4, Video-cassette RL00703-Umatic-013)
  - Kawasaki--Rocky :60, 1982 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL00703-Umatic-014)
  - Kawasaki--Spectre :30, 1982 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL00703-Umatic-015)
  - Monroe--Compilation, undated (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL00703-Umatic-016)
    Includes: Bandit :30 and :15; Shock Tails :30 and :15
  - Monroe--Shock absorbers work prints :30 and :15, undated (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL00703-Umatic-017)
  - Pepsi--International and historical (BBDO), 1983 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL00703-Umatic-018)
  - Pepsi--Pepsi Challenge, Canadian historical, 1983 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL00703-Umatic-019)
    Includes: Stephen Lampman; Corrine Haddad; Frances Schmitt; Barbara Mallins and family; David King; Pat Wymes; Klondike Days; Mosport; Highland Games; Across Canada; Moments; Sharing; Fun; Montage; Cowboy; Local Challenger
  - Ford--Wagon Out in Front 14 spots, 1983 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL00703-Umatic-020)
  - Pepsi--World Over, undated (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL00703-Umatic-021)
  - Presentation reel, 1981 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL00703-Umatic-022)
    Includes: Seven-Up "Thank You America," "Tastefully Yours," "Intermission," "Peeling"; Oscar Mayer "Marching Song"; Food Play; Rose Bowl Float
  - Seven-Up--Historical reel 1967-1976; 24 spots (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL00703-Umatic-023)
  - Seven-Up spot announcements, undated (Box AV6, Audio-phonodisc RL00703-PD-001)